<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevGin</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DevGin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Get to the Point - Software vs. Power Point Presentations</title>
      <link>/post/get-to-the-point-software-vs-power-point-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/get-to-the-point-software-vs-power-point-presentations/</guid>
      <description>I see presentation after presentation about how good their software is or their customized solution to their problem. However, they never get to the point and show me how to solve my problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two-Year Vs Base Year and Option Contract</title>
      <link>/post/two-year-vs-base-year-and-option-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/two-year-vs-base-year-and-option-contract/</guid>
      <description>To assume less risk, the government likes to have the option to have the second year contract exercised, or not. It&amp;rsquo;s a win for the government and it will speed up the acquisition process. This is beecause the government does wish to exercise the option, it will cost almost no administrative burden to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Software Development without Project Managers</title>
      <link>/post/it-software-development-without-project-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/it-software-development-without-project-managers/</guid>
      <description>Who will to do all the administrative work that goes with running projects? Far too many projects start with the lack of a team and lack of project managers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Overview - Cradle to Grave</title>
      <link>/post/contracts-overview-cradle-to-grave/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/contracts-overview-cradle-to-grave/</guid>
      <description>You have a bona fide business need. There is a pain-point in the business community that can be solved with some Commercial Off the Shelf (COT) technology. You do the research and discover a certain software brand name that can solve the problem. How do you go from zero, nada, scratch, to an implemented solution?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Goals &amp; Navigating Red Tape in the Technology Industry 2021</title>
      <link>/post/career-goals-navigating-red-tape-in-the-technology-industry-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/career-goals-navigating-red-tape-in-the-technology-industry-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to share ways to start your year off right with some high-tech career goal advice. Especially within the tech industry, where there are record-level employment opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>