<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on DevGin</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on DevGin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advance your Government Career - E1 to GS-14 (My Path)</title>
      <link>/post/government-career-e1-to-gs-14-my-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/government-career-e1-to-gs-14-my-path/</guid>
      <description>How to Ddvance in the Government – from E-1 to GS-14 The government is finally jumping on the emerging technologies bandwagon. The public sector wants to catch up to where industry is, and fast. In today’s government, there is a push hiring a tech talented workforce. The government sector really prides itself on hiring and empowering diverse people to deliver better services. One thing is for sure, to innovate, it starts with streamlining the procurement process can ensure quicker adoption to new tech in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swissgear 1900 ScanSmart Laptop Backpack Best Review Video</title>
      <link>/post/swissgear-1900-scansmart-laptop-backpack-best-review-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/swissgear-1900-scansmart-laptop-backpack-best-review-video/</guid>
      <description>Pack your Gear The Scansmart Laptop Backpack is one of my most viewed YouTube videos. I have owned two of these now. My YouTube video of the review was such a big hit, I decided to write a blog about.
Before I dive into the details, I want to share a few comments I’ve receieved over the years. The comments might motivate you to give the video a quick watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get to the Point - Software vs. Power Point Presentations</title>
      <link>/post/get-to-the-point-software-vs-power-point-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/get-to-the-point-software-vs-power-point-presentations/</guid>
      <description>I see presentation after presentation about how good their software is or their customized solution to their problem. However, they never get to the point. They end up showing me how to solve their own problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two-Year Vs Base Year and Option Contract</title>
      <link>/post/two-year-vs-base-year-and-option-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/two-year-vs-base-year-and-option-contract/</guid>
      <description>To assume less risk, the government likes to have the option to choose if the second year contract is exercised. It&amp;rsquo;s a win for the government and it will speed up the acquisition process. This is beecause the government does wish to exercise the option, it will cost almost no administrative burden to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Software Development without Project Managers</title>
      <link>/post/it-software-development-without-project-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/it-software-development-without-project-managers/</guid>
      <description>Who will to do all the administrative work that goes with running projects? Far too many projects start with the lack of a team and lack of project managers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Overview - Cradle to Grave</title>
      <link>/post/contracts-overview-cradle-to-grave/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/contracts-overview-cradle-to-grave/</guid>
      <description>You have a bona fide business need. There is a pain-point in the business community that can be solved with some Commercial Off the Shelf (COT) technology. You do the research and discover a certain software brand name that can solve the problem. How do you go from zero, nada, scratch, to an implemented solution?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Goals &amp; Navigating Red Tape in the Technology Industry 2021</title>
      <link>/post/career-goals-navigating-red-tape-in-the-technology-industry-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/career-goals-navigating-red-tape-in-the-technology-industry-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to share ways to start your year off right with some high-tech career goal advice. Especially within the tech industry, where there are record-level employment opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>